http://www.shopzoo.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
OVERVIEW
The Zoological Society of San Diego D/B/A San Diego Zoo Global (“SDZ Global”, “Our”, “Us” or “We”), operates www.sandiegozoo.org, www.sdzsafaripark.org, www.endextinction.org, www.zoomember.com, www.sandiegozookids.org, and www.sandiegozooglobal.org (the “Websites”) and recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of the users of these Websites. Except when express permission is specifically and knowingly provided by you, the website user (“User”, “You” or “Your”), SDZ Global collects no personally identifying information about individuals.  The name, address, and payment information (if applicable) that a User might provide when using these Websites may be processed or disclosed by SDZ Global as permitted under the Websites’ respective Terms of Use, which a User agrees to upon utilizing the information and services of the Websites.  It is necessary to gather certain information from You in order to provide an efficient and pleasant shopping experience.  By using a number of security technologies in our Websites, We maintain, as a priority, the privacy of your information.  We also adhere to strict policies in attempting to prevent the unauthorized use of your personal information.  Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Our Websites and not to our sponsors’ or third-party partners’ websites to which We link.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND SHARING
We utilize cookies, which are small pieces of information sent to your web browser by a website that you visit.  Used as a method of tracking, cookies also enable SDZ Global to relate a visitor’s use of SDZ Global information to any information that a visitor may have specifically and knowingly provided to SDZ Global.  Any such voluntarily provided information, if applicable, may be used by SDZ Global for editorial, marketing, or promotional purposes.  You can set your browser to not accept cookies from Our Websites or other websites you may visit.  By doing so, however, some websites or portions of websites may not function properly. By using Our Websites and not disabling cookies, You consent to allowing their use for the purposes described in this policy.
In addition to cookies, information We collect from You is used to help us monitor site usage and traffic patterns of Our customers to the extent that it serves Our business purposes.  SDZ Global will maintain safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of Your information.  Statistical aggregate information, as well as personal information, is collected for internal and administrative purposes.  Any public disclosure of aggregate information regarding site usage and traffic, which is necessary for business marketing and advertising purposes, is always devoid of any personally identifying information.
The personally identifiable information that You provide to Us and information about any order that you place on our Websites may be combined with other of Your personally identifiable information from Our records and other sources. This information will be used to make Our future marketing efforts to You more efficient. This information may also be shared with our carefully selected third-party service providers and other marketers whose products or services We feel may be of interest to You.  Once We share your information with a third-party, such information becomes subject to such third-party’s privacy practices
The use of cookies and basic information can be used for the targeting and retargeting of messages across various websites for internet-based advertising. This includes sharing cookie data and basic information with third-party advertising vendors for the optimization of marketing campaigns. Examples of information which may be automatically collected include type of operating system, type of browser, the User’s IP address, the User’s website visits before and after coming to Our Websites, UDID (mobile devices), links clicked, and standard server log information.
To opt out of information sharing for the purpose of advertising, please contact 619-718-3000 with your request.
CHILDREN AND PRIVACY
SDZ Global is concerned about protecting children’s privacy. If You are under the age of 13, We do not want your personal information.  Please do not submit any personal information to Us.  We encourage parents to actively protect their children’s privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information to any individual or organization without parental permission.  SDZ Global will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.  If we become aware that a child under 13 years of age has provided us with such information without consent, we will take appropriate action to remove such information from our files.  If a parent or guardian becomes aware that a child under 13 years of age has provided such information to us, he or she should contact us at San Diego Zoo Global, Attention:  Donor Privacy Policy, P.O. Box 120271, San Diego, CA 92112.  There may be some areas within Our Websites where people may post messages or provide feedback, but those under the age of 13 children are again discouraged from providing any personal information.  If a visitor known to be a child (younger than 13) sends an e-mail to SDZ Global, We will only use it to respond to the e-mail and not to create profiles or otherwise retain the information.
SECURE SHOPPING
SDZ Global has incorporated the latest Internet technological standards into the design of the secure purchase areas of its Websites. We also monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to access, upload, or change information on the Websites and across Our network.  Under no uncertain terms, any information You send us while within the secure shipping area is protected by 128-bit “Secure Socket Layer” SSL encryption, making Your transaction safe and reliable.  You can tell whether you are in our secure shopping area by viewing the “lock” or “key” at the bottom of your browser—an unlocked or broken key (depending on your browser) means you are in an unsecured area.
Shopping on the Internet is safe, and online credit card transactions are no more risky than other means of shopping. Our encryption methods make credit card fraud even more difficult than mail or phone orders, or even in-person purchases.  If You experience fraudulent use of your credit card as a result of using Our Websites, notify your credit card company per its rules and procedures.  Most credit card companies will either cover the fraudulent purchases or hold you liable for no more than $50.
As a standard Internet practice, should your credit card company hold you liable for some portion of a fraudulent charge stemming from Our Website(s),  We will reimburse You for the maximum liability of $50, provided the purchase was made through Our secure server.
SDZ Global requires the use of Your name, e-mail address, shipping address, and credit card number/expiration date in order to process and fulfill Your order.  We might also request additional information that you choose to submit about your interests or feedback about our Website(s) and products so that We can provide a better shopping experience for You.  The name, address, and payment information that a User might provide when using Our Websites may be processed or disclosed by SDZ Global as permitted under such Website’s Terms of Use, to which the User agrees to upon utilizing the information and services of the Websites.
YOUR CONSENT AND CHANGES TO POLICY
By using our Website(s), You consent to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.  This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time.  Please check this page periodically for any changes.  Your continued use of Our Website(s) following the posting of any changes constitutes Your acceptance of the changes.
DONOR PRIVACY POLICY
Introduction
The Zoological Society of San Diego D/B/A San Diego Zoo Global (“SDZ Global”, “Our” “We”, or “Us”) is committed to respecting the privacy of Our donors and members.  This Donor Privacy Policy (“Donor Policy”) outlines how SDZ Global collects, uses and protects donor information and exists in conjunction with SDZ Global’s internet privacy policy found at www.sandiegozoo.org.
This Donor Policy covers donor information we collect through the mail, over the phone, onsite at our facilities, offsite at SDZ Global events and online through our Websites and was created to provide confidence as you donate, visit, join, or use our services.  It also demonstrates our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy.
With respect to our donation and membership fundraising practices, we abide by The Association of Fundraising Professional’s (AFP) Donor Bill of Rights, which requires that we handle all information about our donors and members with respect and with confidentiality to the full extent provided by law.
AFP Donor Bill of Rights
1.    To be informed of the organization's mission, of the way the organization intends to use donated resources, and of its capacity to use donations effectively for their intended purposes.
2.    To be informed of the identity of those serving on the organization's governing board, and to expect the board to exercise prudent judgment in its stewardship responsibilities.
3.    To have access to the organization's most recent financial statements.
4.    To be assured their gifts will be used for the purposes for which they were given.
5.    To receive appropriate acknowledgment and recognition.
6.    To be assured that information about their donations is handled with respect and with confidentiality to the extent provided by law.
7.    To expect that all relationships with individuals representing organizations of interest to the donor will be professional in nature.
8.    To be informed whether those seeking donations are volunteers, employees of the organization or hired solicitors.
9.    To have the opportunity for their names to be deleted from mailing lists that an organization may intend to share.
10.To feel free to ask questions when making a donation and to receive prompt, truthful and forthright answers.
Donor Information Collection and Sharing
SDZ Global will collect donor and member information when processing monetary or in-kind donations, establishing SDZ Global membership, completing online purchases, registering for SDZ Global programs or events and when providing customer or donor stewardship services.  We may use your information to send you transactional receipts, renewal notices, upgrade offers, park updates and newsletters, as well as occasional mailings and emails about SDZ Global and its programs that We think might be of interest to you.
SDZ Global may share donor and member information with Our third-party service providers to help us steward, retain and expand our donor and membership base.  These services may include membership marketing and fulfillment, membership processing and data analytics.
The personally identifiable information that you provide to us, along with donor transactional information may be combined with other personally identifiable information and transaction information from our records and other sources to help us carry out Our legitimate business purposes.
Donor Opt-Out
SDZ Global provides you with the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive donor communications from Us, direct mail offers, telemarketing offers, emails or updates, or if you do not want Us to share your personally identifiable information with our third-party service providers.  To opt out, please write to San Diego Zoo Global, Attention:  Opt Out, P.O Box 120271, San Diego, CA. 92112.  This will prevent the sharing of your donor information and will cease all communications not required by law.
SDZ Global also reserves the right to disclose your information in circumstances that SDZ Global deems necessary or appropriate, such as to respond to a legal process or request from a governmental agency.
Consent and Changes To Our Donor Privacy Policy
You consent to this Donor Privacy Policy when making a donation to SDZ Global, purchasing SDZ Global membership products or services, visiting our facilities, conducting donor transactions through the mail, onsite or through our Call Center or by accessing Our Websites.  We reserve the right to revise this Donor Privacy Policy at any time.  Please visit www.sandiegozoo.org for the most current version of our Donor Privacy Policy or write to us at San Diego Zoo Global, Attention:  Donor Privacy Policy, P.O. Box 120271, San Diego, CA 92112.
Effective date:  3/19/2018
Subscribe Sign up for the latest from SHOPZOO.
